(Baggage Clerk:)bags are misrouted.
(Howard:)All right, fine.
Where did you misroute
(Howard:)the only woman
who ever loved me?
(Howard:)The first... well,
first, I meant first.
(Clerk:)I just need some information.
(Clerk:)Uh, what's the flight number?
816.
(Howard:)I really did mean first.
(Bernadette:)Just drop it.
(Clerk:)And can you describe the bag?
(Bernadette:)Um, well,
(Bernadette:)it's, uh, black.
(Bernadette:)There's a red ribbon
tied to the handle...
(Howard:)The world's greatest mom
is in the shoe compartment!
(Sheldon:)You ready to begin?
(Penny:)Yup. Be right there.
(Penny:)I assume you don't want wine.
(Sheldon:)Correct. You're not
supposed to drink alcohol
(Sheldon:)when operating heavy machinery.
(Penny:)What heavy machinery?
(Penny:)Let's just start.
(Sheldon:)Well, as a Texas gentleman,
(Sheldon:)I'm inclined to
say ladies first.
(Sheldon:)Although, I'm concerned that
level of politeness and charm
(Sheldon:)might make you fall in love with
me before the test even begins.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps we should flip a coin.
(Sheldon:)Or if you're familiar
with the rules
(Sheldon:)of Rock, Paper, Scissors...